This video is for you to introduce the materials and the related update of the rendering
Through our new part of the storage function
You can now save the selected version and material as a clothing file
ZPLC format for storage rather than storing the entire project
Choose the version to be stored in the 2D window
Find the storage in the file
Click on the clothing, select
Enter the file name and click Save
Let's repeat the above operations to store the hat version
You can see that the clothes file just saved has been stored separately
I will show you how to save and store the clothes
The previous user must manually delete
Can be stored after the unnecessary elements
Now you can only save the necessary part to simplify the work process
At the same time, it is not interrupted when continuing to process the complete file
Especially in making a reusable
It is more convenient to use when the version and clothing assets are stored
In order to improve the efficiency of the project
Now the hard drive in the new version can be leaked
This update makes the surface of all print cloths look more harmonious and can present a more accurate lighting pattern and shadow effect after rendering.
Select the fabric and click Add Print.
Now we can see that in default state, the fabric pattern and the print pattern use two types of stickers.
Now if you want to use the same sticker pattern as the print cloth and the print cloth,
you can select the same pattern pattern as the fabric pattern in the attribute editor.
This function is also used for transparent,
and you can also select the same pattern pattern as the print cloth and the print cloth in the attribute editor.
The fabric pattern and print cloth use the same PBR sticker pattern.
This allows you to present all the design elements with a unified light and texture effect.
This is a perfect choice for designers who pursue high precision and detail.
In the previous hollow version,
the contrast ratio of the print cloth and the print cloth in the print cloth will lead to some visual errors.
In the new version,
the hollow has increased the accurate control of the key print parameters,
and the print cloth has a truly clear presentation of the print cloth effect in this print cloth,
which significantly improves the readability and accuracy.
Activate Print Cloth Render.
You can see that there is an additional information prompt next to the print cloth.
Zoom in to check the details of the print cloth.
Navigate to the attribute editor of the print cloth.
First, use the double needle print cloth as an example.
You can see that there is an additional part-time model ratio below.
Activate it.
Set the following print cloth parameters to adjust the effect of the original print cloth pattern percentage.
Length
Adjust the length of the needle.
Assign the position of the thumb and right finger of the pin.
penetration
Set the penetration pressure.
The measured frequency of the needle is set to the minimum at the bottom in the allotment pattern
Then you can see the changes in the settings
Adjust the distance between the name line and the edge of the applied line
Control the visual thickness of the real line
Set the width of the name line
Note that this parameter is more suitable for the type of name line with width
Such as the edge of the left-hand side and so on
So I switch to the name line of the applied line here to demonstrate
Adjust the distance between the name line and the edge of the applied line
Set multiple name lines
Change back the double-edged name line display
All the changes are only visible when the model image rendering is in active state
And will not affect the parameters of the actual name line itself
After closing the model image rendering
All content will return to the normal view
In the previous version
When opening the self-defined viewing pin image
You can only output the self-defined viewing pin image of each color
Can't pin the color of the specific viewing
In the 2025.1 version, you can choose the self-defined viewing
Based on the color of the desired viewing pin image
Open the rendering window
In the image attribute settings
Change the viewing period to the self-defined viewing
At this time, the color is current
You can see the following storage settings
In the settings
There will be a selection of the self-defined viewing pin image
Open the selection to render
Will output the color of the flag
The pin image under the self-defined viewing
This is the same as before
Or keep the viewing setting as the self-defined viewing
Change the color of the flag from the current flag to the full flag
You can also click on the self-defined color you want to choose on the right side
When you choose more than one flag
There will be a flag pin image option at the bottom
And the bottom added the option to select the self-defined viewing angle
This also means
In addition to the self-defined viewing pin image of each flag
You can also combine the flag rendering image of a selected viewing angle
For example, I chose the viewing angle 5 here
After completing the settings, click on the final rendering rendering image
You will get the self-defined viewing angle pin image of each flag
And the color pin image under the selected viewing angle
Based on this update
Users can more freely combine the color rendering image of the self-defined viewing angle
To increase the efficiency of work